Welcome back to where the magic began.
Harry Potter 20th Anniversary: Return to Hogwarts is a
documentary film directed by Joe Pearlman.
An enchanting making-of story told through all-new in-depth interviews and cast conversations, inviting fans
on a magical first-person journey through one of the most beloved film franchises of all time.
Self, played by Daniel Radcliffe.
Self, played by Rupert Grint.
Self, played by Emma Watson.
Self, played by Bonnie Wright.
Self, played by Matthew Lewis.
Self, played by Tom Felton.
Harry Potter 20th Anniversary: Return to Hogwarts is a television
special released on 1 January 2022 on HBO Max.
It is a reunion special for the cast and crew of the Harry Potter film series, marking the
twentieth anniversary of the series' first instalment, The Philosopher's Stone.
It was produced by Warner Bros.
Unscripted Television in association with Warner Horizon
and executive produced by Casey Patterson.
The films' protagonist trio Daniel Radcliffe, Rupert Grint, and Emma Watson appear throughout the special, along with surviving principal cast members Helena Bonham Carter, Robbie Coltrane, Ralph Fiennes, Jason Isaacs, Gary Oldman, Tom Felton,
James Phelps, Oliver Phelps, Mark Williams, Bonnie Wright, Alfred Enoch, Ian Hart, Toby Jones, Matthew Lewis, and Evanna Lynch, producer David Heyman, and filmmakers Chris Columbus, Alfonso Cuarón, Mike Newell, and David Yates.
The special is also notable for marking Coltrane's final on-screen
appearance prior to his death on 14 October 2022.
The film explores themes of reunion, fantasy world, social
gathering, college reunion, cinema history.